(Penny:)Like there's a difference.
(Leonard:)There's a big difference.
(Penny:)Arrow.
(Leonard:)Lantern.
(Penny:)Whatever. Look,
if Zack and I had just gone
(Penny:)to a regular club or a party,
it would have been fine,
(Penny:)but this, with the costumes,
and you...
(Leonard:)What about me?
(Penny:)Nothing.
(Penny:)Let's go to the party.
(Penny:)How do I look?
(Sheldon:)Um...
(Leonard:)I guarantee you'll be
the prettiest girl there.
(Howard(outside the door):)Okay, the good news is,
we have a Wonder Woman.
(Leonard:)Oh.
Yes.
(Sheldon:)What's the bad news?
(Howard:)Superman probably isn't
(Howard:)getting laid tonight.
(Zack:)Aw, damn.
(Stuart:)And the award
(Stuart:)for best group costume
goes to...